[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "Nima, what is the latest in terms of whether this operation is still ongoing, how many terrorist do you think is still alive, and how many people we may think have actually died in reality here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "Well, the latest from the Kenyan Authority is that they believe this is the end-game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Becky Anderson"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "IN", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "EX", ",", "CD", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What do we know about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, the Kenyan Foreign Minister told Connect the World, Becky Anderson, on CNN that not only did she believe that there were Americans but there were also Brits, there were other Western European nationalities in there as well, that Al Shabaab has been quite boastfully claiming since the beginning of this attack that there were three Americans in there, one Canadian, a Finnish person, and a Brit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Tell me, first of all, how is your brother?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "He is well and he is safe and fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "What did he do when this attack started?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "He works as a computer engineer, that is the work he does and he's designated as a computer engineer in the mall, and he works with cameras that - with the security cameras.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What does he told you about the incident he saw from what he saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "One of the things he said is he was pretty terrified because he has never seen anybody shoot anyone apart from TV, in a movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "And did he seem to be completely indiscriminate because there was a suggestion that they were only targeting non-Muslims, but from what your brother saw, it seem like they were killing almost anybody they found?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "There was a -- the Muslim at one point were told they could leave, and they shot everybody else.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Al Shabaab"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "But either way, one of the worst terror attacks of recent years, what do we know about the perpetrators?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Well, Al Shabaab movement started as a nationalistic movement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "Yeah, do we think that this may have been connected to that, are the acting at his direction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, I think there was a lot of interesting similarities between (inaudible) Ayman al-Zawahiri instructed Al Qaeda affiliates to do, and what they did, they said, \"Attack Western target.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "If that turns out to be true, what does that tell us about Al Shabaab and also Al Qaeda now in terms of how far it spreads?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I mean, this is very interesting.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "And would they all be from Somalian origin, originally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "It's a combination.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "I mean, is Al-Qaeda now just as kind of (inaudible) entity which many, many terror groups are now operating under?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["8 percent"], "LOCATION": ["Somalia", "Syria"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CD", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "So Nick, (inaudible) some kind of big picture context, what is the link between what we saw happened in Kenya, what you've seen happening in Syria, you just got back from Syria, is there a context in which all this comes together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "You know, I do think that they're (inaudible) I mean, if you push me to make linkages, one can talk about a youth ball which tends to make countries very unstable, that every extra percentage of young man you have between age 15 and 24 increases by something like 8 percent, the risk of civil conflict that's certainly a problem in Somalia, it's a problem in Syria, lack of education, lack of employment opportunities, and there are jihadi elements in both countries.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nick"], "LOCATION": ["Kenya", "Syria", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "What is America do about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I think that it could indeed happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "But, what does (inaudible) on the ground?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "WP", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "You know Piers, I got to say that when you're out there on the border talking to these kids, the face of a Syrian refugee today is a child's face, half of them are children.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "I mean these things are a huge leap of faith in your mind are they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Minneapolis", "Somalia", "Southern Part of Somalia", "Minneapolis"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", ",", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Tell me about the case you are involved in and what your reaction is to what has happened in Kenya as a result?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "CC", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Well, we were involved in representing a man who was accused of helping, convinced and transport young men from a mosque in Minneapolis to travel to Somalia ultimately to participate and attend in a training camp run by Al Shabaab in Southern Part of Somalia and the case was tried in federal district court here in Minneapolis and our client was found client was found guilty.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Kenya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "But John Hopeman if I can come to you, in terms of the events in Kenya, does it entirely surprise you given what you learned about this whole operation during the case that you are acting in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Well, no it doesn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Hopeman"], "LOCATION": ["Kenya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "How do you target the Somali connection in Minneapolis in particular?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "Well, I mean the solution -- you can't protect every mall, every public gathering.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Minneapolis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Now, we're getting to the end of this trial, do you think that Conrad Murray maybe vindicated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I think he'll be vindicated in some sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What have we learned new in this civil action that we maybe didn't hear in the criminal case that could change people's thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "POS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Well, a lot of evidence that was excluded at the criminal trial came out in the civil trial such as evidence of Michael Jackson's dire financial situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackson"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJS", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "For the civil trial, what is the significance of that new material that was in this particular case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, I certainly think that it points that Jackson is culpable for his own death or at least to a large degree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Where do you see his own culpability as being inarguable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, I believe that he may have done some things that were viewed as negligent, but I do not believe that he is responsible for Michael's death -- for Michael Jackson's death in any way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Because you think that Michael Jackson was 50 years old, him being taking these kinds of drugs for a very long time, and was quite persistent in making sure that he got them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "How was he dealing with the damaged to his reputation and the public hostility that comes when you are deemed culpable for the death of a legend like Michael Jackson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "It's very difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jackson", "Jackson", "Michael Jackson"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Does he wish he'd never got involved with Michael Jackson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Well, I think that would be illogical conclusion, and Jackson was his friend, but he did not know the situation in which he found himself and he has stated many times that if he knew that Jackson was a drug addict, he never would have given up his practices to become Michael Jackson's personal physician.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "Piers, Propofol is used every minute of the day in hospitals all over the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "In terms of where this action itself just taking it in isolation, what do you expect the verdict to be from all that we've heard in terms of evidence?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, I think there are two questions, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "In terms of his own personal responsibility for the circumstances leading up to his death, where does Michael Jackson's own accountability (ph) come into play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Well, look, there's been evidence that he obtained a lot of prescription drugs from pharmacies and physicians, there's been evidence that he use propofol, but he didn't die, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["70 percent"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "CD", "NN", ",", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Do you agree with him on most things political?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "NNS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I agree with him on probably 70 percent, maybe 75.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "It just looks to me like they can't make up their minds what they really want to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Yes, it's very splintered.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 372, "question": "How do you as a party do you think move to becoming in agreement and more electable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I have been thinking this for years that we have to start coming to terms with the trends that are changing in America, gay marriage has already won, I think it's completely a topic that we have won and that people are just going to have to deal with, but there's a lot of people in a Republican Party that really want to claim to the past (ph) and every time people say, \"I am a bad republican and your father was too moderate.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeb Bush", "Bush"], "LOCATION": ["Phoenix"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "-NONE-", "NN", ":", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Who do you see out these as potentially a candidate in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "CCAIN: This is so tricky, I was actually at my dad's birthday party a few weeks ago in Phoenix having this conversation with his old campaign manager and a few other people that have been in his political circle for a while and they said (ph) point to Jeb Bush, but I still think the Bush name is pretty tainted and I think he is much more conservative than people really realize.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie", "Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 380, "question": "Chris Christie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 381, "answer": "I use to love Chris Christie; I'm kind of done with Chris Christie right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VB", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "You know ever since his speech of the convention, I don't know if you remember it was so -- you know, he just talk about himself the entire time and I think politicians obviously, there's at some level of self-promotion that you have to do but I would like the next leader of the Republican Party and the next nominee to maybe be a little more interested in helping the country than just their platform.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Now, in your show you do a sort of big issue every episode, one of them is feminism, (inaudible) Billy Ray Cyrus about his daughter Miley and her twerking wrecking bold sensation that's galvanize the world, are you a twerker, do you twerk?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "No, no one wants to see me twerk.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Ray Cyrus", "Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley Cyrus"], "LOCATION": ["Playboy"]}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 391, "question": "Is it somebody just using them with their feminist (inaudible) to challenge people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 392, "answer": "I ask this question, can you -- you know, I'm a woman who has done interviews in Playboy, I like dressing provocatively, I like attention from men from time to time, can I do all these things to be feminist just that question have been controversial, I think Miley Cyrus is young and she is learning about her sexuality, I have no problem with anything she has done and I think the criticism on her is a lot of it is unwarranted to be a woman in American is to be controversial especially if you are a pop star.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130923pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Do you think mom can be a politician?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "I don't think mom could be a politician, I think our mother is the greatest politician's wife in the history of the free world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]